ANDRES GUERRERO

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER / MECHATRONIC ENGINEER

guerrero9510@hotmail.com Medellín, Antioquia, COL (+57) 3174957012 www.github.com/andresguerrero270895 www.linkedin.com/in/andres-guerrero-00862a217/

Professional Profile

Full Stack Developer with a background as a Mechatronics Engineer. Experience working in Node.js, React, PostgreSQL and WordPress. I am a resilient person, curious, autodidactic, with high capacity to analyze and solve problems, take initiative and teamwork. Knowledge in agile methodologies, GIT, data structure, algorithms and **CSS** frameworks

Work Experience

Front End Developer WordPress

Digital Marketing - Medellín, Antioquia

- Design landing pages
- Plan advertising campaigns

Agust 2021 - Current

Developer Node.js Freelancer

CorkInc - USA, Remote

- Build API Servers
- Maintain website

March 2022 - September 2022

Educational background

Full Stack Web Developer

Henry - Remote

Technologies: JavaScript, HTML, CSS, NodeJS, Express, React, Redux and PostgreSQL.

February 2022 - September 2022

Degree in Engineer Mechatronic

Institución Universitaria ITM

Technologies: Programming and maintenance of PLC's, management of the TIA PORTAL program.

February 2013 - October 2021

English

SMART Academy

Level: B2 - Upper Intermediate

References

Mark Cornelius O'Leary

Senior Software Engineer en CorkInc

Phone Contact: +57 3008106209

+1 4256501580

Santiago Vanegas Perez

Senior Technician en Endava

Phone Contact: +57 3113907898